

# **ERKUT KAYA**

Candidate Web Developer

+90 531 515 82 28

erkut.kaya@outlook.com

linkedin.com/erkut-kaya

### **Creative Skills**

Teamwork

Googling

Problem Solving

# Software Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Bootstrap

ReactJS

SQL C++

C#

### Tools

Visual Studio

Visual Studio Code

MS Office

Microsoft SQL Server

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Premiere Pro

## **Profile**

I am a 4th year student of Computer Engineering department at Eskisehir Osmangazi University. I want to follow the technological developments in the field of technology and digitalization, make improvements in the system, improve customer satisfaction and loyalty, and improve the user experience.

## **Education**

2017-Present Eskisehir Osmangazi University (Eskisehir)

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

2012-2016 Ertugrul Kurdoglu High School (Kocaeli)

2004-2012 Ibni Sina Primary School (İstanbul)

# **Experience**

09/2021 - 10/2021 Intern / Anadolu University, Eskisehir

- Focused on website design and software development using Html, Css, JavaScript, Excel and Adobe Photoshop.

07/2021 - 08/2021 Intern / Anadolubank, Istanbul

- Built a representative web application of banking using Html, Css, JavaScript, Bootstrap and ReactJS.

# **Certificates**

### Udemy

Front End Web Development Bootcamp (October 2021)

#### **BTK Akademi**

Project Management (October 2021)

### **BTK Akademi**

Introduction to Social Media Specialist (October 2021)

### Google

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing (September 2021)

#### **BTK Akademi**

Availability of Websites (September 2021)

### Cisco

Networking Essentials (Jun 2021)

## **Hobbies**

- ChessWalking
- Music
- Video Games
- Cycling
- Drawing

## **Preferences**

### Dr. Şahin IŞIK

Assistant Proffessor, Eskisehir Osmangazi University **Email:** sahini@ogu.edu.tr